Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Department of Theatre Records, 1911-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1911-2015, UWM Archival Collection 85; 14.3 cubic ft. (23 boxes)
  - 2. Production Files, 1911-2015, The production photographs consist of a mix of 8x10, 5x7, 4x6, and 3x5 sizes. Unless otherwise stated, all of the negatives are 35 mm safety film.
    - 1960-1969
      - The Misanthrope, May 1967 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - The Investigation, July 1967 (Box 7, Folder 49)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Taliped, October 1967
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Juno and the Paycock, November 1967 (Box 7, Folder 50)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Lovers in A Subway, November 1967
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Ransom of the Red Chief, December 1967 (Box 7, Folder 51)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Studio Series Productions, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Division St. America, February 1968 (Box 7, Folder 53)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Man of La Mancha, February 1968
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Matinee Theatre, March 1968
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 54)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - An Evening with Pinter and Bradbury, April 1968 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - The Bacchae, May 1968 (Box 7, Folder 56)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 11)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - The Tenant, May 1968 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Harper's Ferry, July 1968 (Box 7, Folder 58)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Empire Builders, October 1968 (Box 7, Folder 59)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Flibbertygibbet, November 1968 (Box 7, Folder 60)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - The Zoo Story, November 1968 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - A Man's Man, December 1968 (Box 7, Folder 62)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Intil the Land, January 1969 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - A Roaring Good Time, March 1969 (Box 7, Folder 64)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Dance of Death, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 65)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Journey, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - The Balcony, July 1969 (Box 7, Folder 67)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Summertree, October 1969 (Box 7, Folder 68)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Dracula, December 1969 (Box 7, Folder 69)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 1970-1979
      - Studio Series Productions, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 70-71)
      - Acid Rock Opera, February 1970
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - New Lamps for Old, February 1970 (Box 7, Folder 72)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - To All Things Black and Beautiful, February 1970 (Box 7, Folder 73)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - The Love-Wait Happening, March 1970 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Tamberlaine the Great, March 1970 (Box 7, Folder 75)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Measures Taken, April 1970 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Three in Bed, April 1970
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Who's Got His Own, May 1970 (Box 7, Folder 77)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Twelfth Night, July 1970 (Box 7, Folder 78)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Life is a Dream, October 1970 (Box 7, Folder 79)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Three Cheers for Nothing: The American Dream, Striptease, and Picnic on the Battlefield, October 1970 (Box 7, Folder 80)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Alice in Wonderland, November 1970 (Box 7, Folder 81)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Helen in Egypt and Medea, November 1970 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      - Little Murders, December 1970 (Box 7, Folder 83)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Great International Magic Show, 1971-1979 (Box 7, Folder 84)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - The Tavern, February 1971 (Box 7, Folder 85)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - On a Clear Day (Cudahy HS Matinee), March 1971
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, April 1971 (Box 7, Folder 86)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - The Beggar's Opera, May 1971 (Box 7, Folder 87)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - American Nightmares: Rats, The Sandbox, and Dutchman, July 1971 (Box 7, Folder 88)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - LUV, July 1971 (Box 7, Folder 89)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Fortune and Men's Eyes, August 1971 (Box 7, Folder 90)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - What the Butler Saw, August 1971 (Box 7, Folder 91)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Sergeant Musgrave's Dance, October 1971 (Box 7, Folder 92)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Breakfast with Santa, November 1971
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Sacramento Fifty Miles, November 1971 (Box 7, Folder 93)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - The Serpent, November 1971 (Box 7, Folder 94)
      - A Thurber Carnival, November 1971 (Box 7, Folder 95)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Hamlet, December 1971 (Box 7, Folder 96)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Lovers, December 1971 (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Marat Sade, February 1972 (Box 7, Folder 98)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Philadelphia Here I Come, March 1972 (Box 7, Folder 99)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Man of La Mancha, April 1972 (Box 7, Folder 100)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Twain by Twain, June 1972 (Box 7, Folder 101)
      - Cream City Cuckolds, October 1972 (Box 7, Folder 102)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Livin De Life, October 1972 (Box 7, Folder 103)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, October 1972 (Box 7, Folder 104)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Country Wife, November 1972 (Box 7, Folder 105)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - The House of Bernada Alba, November 1972 (Box 7, Folder 106)
      - Hamlet, December 1972 (Box 7, Folder 107)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Hedda Gabler, February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 15)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Reunion of Sam, February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Sleeping Beauty, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - The Devils, April 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Mabou Mines and Pierot, June-July 1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Prima Donna (Opera), June 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Amelia Goes to the Ball, July 1973
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Medea, July 1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - The Life and Death of Sneaky Fitch, September 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 20)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Phaedra, October 1973
        - Production File (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Video and Show Images
      - A Hunger Artist, November 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - You're a Good Man Charlie Brown, November 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - A Servant of Two Masters, December 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Thief/The Pig, December 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Moon for the Misbegotten, February 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - And Miss Reardon Drinks a Little, March 1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Cabaret, March 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - The Urinal and Don't Walk Around Stark Naked, April 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Women Beware Women, April 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - The Dramatization of 365 Days, May 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - The Fourposter, September 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Lemonade and Bedtime Story, October 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - School for Wives, October 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Winterthing, November 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - The Tempest, December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - The Boyfriend, March 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - An Evening of Mime and European Clown, March 1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Caucasion Chalk Circle, April 1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - The Ragtime Years, July 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Tango, October 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Sherlock Holmes, November 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Cinderella, February 1976
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 15)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Misanthrope, February 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - The Miser, March 1976 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Summer Theatre: Return of the Spirit, Summer Strings, The Children's Revolt, Play it Again Sam, Dames at Sea, and Man Oh Man!, April-July 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
      - Night of the Iguana, April 1976 (Box 8, Folder 34)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Marriage of Figaro, March 1977 (Box 8, Folder 35)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Pullman Car Hiawatha, February 1978 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Thovil, March 1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Albert Herring (Opera), April 1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - The Rimers of Eldritch, April 1978 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - This Fair Child of Mine, November 1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Rogues and Vagabonds, November 1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Two One-Act Operas: Riders to the Sea and Gianni Schicchi, April 1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - The Miser, December 1979
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 23)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - 1980-1989
      - Cosi Fan Tutte, January 1980 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, February 1980 (Box 8, Folder 43)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 24)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - The Play's the Thing, March 1980 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - The Three Sisters, May 1980 (Box 8, Folder 45)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 25)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Waiting for Godot, May 1980 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Romeo and Juliet, June-August 1980
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - There Will Be No Trojan War! (Tiger at the Gates), October 1980 (Box 8, Folder 47)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - A Midsummer Nights Dream, November 1980 (Box 8, Folder 48)
        - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Cherry Orchard, December 1980 (Box 8, Folder 49)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - The Lower Depths, February 1981 (Box 8, Folder 50)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - The Bacchae, March 1981 (Box 8, Folder 51)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Buried Child, May 1981 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Tartuffe, May 1981 (Box 8, Folder 53)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Opera Productions, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Wooing, Winning, and Reconciliation, January 1982 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - A Mark Twain Offering: Guthrie Theatre Tour, February 1982 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Summerfolk, September-December 1982
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Landis and Company, October 1982 (Box 8, Folder 58)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Tis a Pity She's a Whore, November 1982 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Ahmal and the Night Visitors, December 1982 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Private Lives, December 1982 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Merry Wives of Windsor, March 1983 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Stratford-on-Downer, April 1983 (Box 8, Folder 63)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
      - Our Town, July 1983 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - The Glass Menagerie, October 1983 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - The Hostage, October 1983 (Box 8, Folder 66)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Major Barbara, November 1983 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - A Cat Among Pidgeons, December 1983 (Box 8, Folder 68)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Bus Stop, February 1984 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - You Can't Take It With You, February 1984 (Box 8, Folder 70)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Richard III, March 1984 (Box 8, Folder 71)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - The Way of the World, April 1984 (Box 8, Folder 72)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Twelfth Night, September-December 1984
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth, November 1984 (Box 8, Folder 73)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Three Centuries of Romance (Opera), November 1984 (Box 23)
      - Arms and the Man, December 1984 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Foxfire, February 1985 (Box 8, Folder 75)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Cherry Orchard, February-May 1985
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - King Lear, April 1985 (Box 8, Folder 76)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - La Boheme, April 1985 (Box 8, Folder 77)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Major Bullshot Gorgeous, October 1985 (Box 8, Folder 78)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Old Explorers, October 1985 (Box 8, Folder 79)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Romeo and Juliet, October 1985 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - An Evening of One Act Comedies, November 1986 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Oedipus the King, December 1985 (Box 8, Folder 82)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - The Rimers of Eldritch, December 1985 (Box 8, Folder 83)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - The Inspector General, February 1986 (Box 8, Folder 84)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Under Milk Wood, February 1986 (Box 8, Folder 85)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - La Ronde, April 1986 (Box 8, Folder 86)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Othello, April 1986 (Box 8, Folder 87)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - The Secret Marriage, April 1986 (Box 8, Folder 88)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - The Good Doctor, October 1986 (Box 8, Folder 89)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - The Importance of Being Earnest, October 1986 (Box 8, Folder 90)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Measure for Measure, November 1986 (Box 8, Folder 91)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - The Hasty Heart, December 1986 (Box 8, Folder 92)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Merrily We Roll Along, December 1986 (Box 8, Folder 93)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - A Doll's House, February 1987 (Box 8, Folder 94)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - The Good Woman of Setzuan, February 1987 (Box 8, Folder 95)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - On the Razzle, March 1987 (Box 8, Folder 96)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Runar and Kyllikki, April 1987 (Box 8, Folder 97)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - The Imaginary Invalid, May 1987 (Box 8, Folder 98)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - The Rivals, October 1987 (Box 8, Folder 99)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Playboy of the Western World, November 1987 (Box 8, Folder 100)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Arms and the Man, April 1988 (Box 8, Folder 101)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Lie of the Mind, April 1988 (Box 8, Folder 102)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - San Francisco Mime Troupe, October 1988 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Red Fox/Second Hangin', November 1988 (Box 8, Folder 104)
      - Great Artist Series, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - King of Hearts, March 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - The Price, October 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - London Assurance, November 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Wild Honey, December 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
        - Poster (Box 23)
    - 1990-1999
      - The Homecoming, January 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Captain Jinks and the Horse Marines, March 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
      - Henry V, March 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
      - International Theatre Training Festival Milwaukee, April 1990
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Blithe Spirit, October 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Caucasion Chalk Circle, October 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - An Enemy of the People, December 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - A Midsummer Nights Dream, December 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Opera Productions, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Man and Superman, February 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 2)
      - Speed the Plow, February 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Translations, March 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Summer and Smoke, May 1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Mass Appeal, September 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Cherry Orchard, October 1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - The Grapes of Wrath, October 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Three Sisters, November 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - The Three Musketeers, December 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 2)
      - Gilgamesh, February 1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Woman in Mind, February 1992 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Romeo and Juliet, February 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 2)
      - Guys and Dolls, May 1992 (Box 9, Folder 28)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 3)
      - A Lesson From Aloes, October 1992 (Box 9, Folder 29)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 3)
      - Mary Rose, December 1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 3)
      - Rocket to the Moon and Come Back Little Sheba, February 1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Twelfth Night, March 1993 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Under Milk Wood, April 1993 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - American Buffalo, October 1993 (Box 9, Folder 35)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Strider, October 1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Merry Wives of Windsor, December 1993 (Box 9, Folder 37)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - View from the Bridge and Desire Under the Elm, February 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Harvey, March 1994 (Box 9, Folder 40)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - A Servant of Two Masters, April 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Summer in the Park Productions, July 1994
        - Blueprints (Oversize 5)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - Poster (Box 23)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Lady of the Sea and The Seagull, October 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Sherlock Holmes, December 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Macbeth, March 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Our Country's Good, March 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 4)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, March 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 3)
      - The Substance of Fire, October 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Cinderella, December 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Back Country Crimes, 02/1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Bus Stop, March 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - The Matchmaker, April 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 4)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - The Line, September 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Miss Julie and The Three Sisters, October 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Great Expectations, December 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - All My Sons and In the Heart of America, February 1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Queen of Carnival and Father of New Orleans, March 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - The Taming of the Shrew, April 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Always... Patsy Cline, August 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Oleanna, October 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Uncle Vanya and Barker's Uncle Vanya, October 1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - You Can't Take It With You, December 1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Lake Street Extension, February 1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - King Lear, March 1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
        - Poster (Box 23)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Bone Violin, April 1998
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - A Hot Wind From the South, April 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - On the Verge, May 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Our Town, December 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
        - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - The Greeks, March 1999 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - The Art of Success and The Smell of Popcorn, April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - The Woods, April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Summer Shakes, July-October 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Ubu, October 1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Tartuffe, December 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
    - 2000-2015
      - Chaim Potok Speaks and Davita's Harp, January 2000
        - Production File (Box 10, Folder 36)
        - Video
      - Midnight and Moll Flanders, February 2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
      - Blithe Spirit, April 2000 (Box 10, Folder 38)
        - Negatives (Box 21)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - End Game, April 2000 (Box 10, Folder 39)
        - Poster (Box 23)
      - Wild Honey, October 2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Sexual Perversity in Chicago, October 2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - A Comedy of Errors, December 2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)